<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Abhijit&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Abhijit&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pex - Python Executable</title>
      <link>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/pex-python-one-file-executable-env/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/pex-python-one-file-executable-env/</guid>
      <description>What is pex pex is a smart utility to create the single file independent Python environment, with which you can run Python based programs just like it is a executable program.
Creating pex to create an environment with pex:
$ pex requests -o myenv.pex   the list of dependencies here is just requests package can add more than one dependencies like below: bash $ pex requests flask etc -o myenv.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using bootstrap-dropdown with Vuejs2</title>
      <link>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/vuejs-and-bootstrap-dropdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/vuejs-and-bootstrap-dropdown/</guid>
      <description>So while, still exploring/playing with Vuejs, came across another peculiar task - making bootstrap&amp;rsquo;s dropdown work with Vuejs, and here is how I make it finally work! (well atleast for me)
Though it seems very straight-forward at first - making the dropdown show or hide based on one flag data attribute. With chrome inspector, I could find out the required css class for same is: open.
But, the challenge was to hide it (remove the open class) once user clicks away outside the dropdown menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using datepicker with Vuejs2</title>
      <link>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/vuejs_and_datepicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/vuejs_and_datepicker/</guid>
      <description>Using datepicker with Vuejs2 Ok, so I am learning/exploring Vuejs now a days. It&amp;rsquo;s a great MVVM framework which is light-weight and simple to learn. Simple enough to start without any background with other similar Javascript frameworks.
After going through initial code samples and tutorials, I wanted to go for more. At around same time, working on one side project, I needed to integrate bootstrap-datepicker with Vuejs. Did some search online, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any working solution along with Vuejs2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Sublime</title>
      <link>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/sublime_is_awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/sublime_is_awesome/</guid>
      <description>Sublime is Awesome I feel sublime text is the most versatile and awesome editor for writing code and in general for any type of text (including markdown).
Why I love it  Small setup size ~5 MB. Works seamlessly across different platforms Windows/Mac/Linux. themes which are easy on eye. Supports syntax highlighting for most of languages out of Box. Has built in spell check functionality. Multiple Cursors. Instead search/replace, select replace multiple occurrences once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abhijit.mamarde.com/post/first_post/</guid>
      <description>Hey reader! Welcome to my blog. I have started this own blogging site finally. I usually scribble to understand a concept better. So, you would find my blogs would contain sort of notes for my own or something I really want to share.
Created with &amp;lt;3 using  Sublime Text3 + MarkdownEditing Hugo Bootstrap  print &amp;quot;Hello World !!!&amp;quot;  CTRL&amp;nbsp;ALT&amp;nbsp;DEL
So let&amp;rsquo;s start  You write, you learn, you learn and you Evolve!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>